

CONTACT



hmdarden97@gmail.com

+1 (479) 329-8640

EDUCATION

 UNIVERSITY OF ARKANSAS AT LITTLE ROCK

WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT - BA
IN PROGRESS- EXPECTED MAY, 2024

GOOGLE- COURSERA

PROJECT MANAGEMENT- CERTIFICATE
IN PROGRESS- EXPECTED MAY, 2024

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JAVASCRIPT

GIT/GITHUB

WORDPRESS

FIGMA

ELEMENTOR

ADOBE CREATIVE CLOUD

SOCIALS









Hannah M. Darden

Web Developer

PROFILE

Current Senior at the University of Arkansas at Little Rock pursing a BA in Web Design and Development, minoring in Information Technology. Diverse experience in HTML/CSS, design, project management, client-customer management and training, computer multitasking, and problem solving. Strong interest and growing skillset in UX/UI design.

INTERNSHIP

Summer 2023

HELP ASSISTANT

EMERGING ANALYTICS CENTER- UALR

Worked on projects for the Art and Web Development teams. Assisted in the creation and maintenance of sites hosted through the center. Received training in new tools and softwares such as Confluence, Blender, and 3Ds Max. Furthered my skillset in sites such as Wordpress and SiteGround.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2023-Present

CENTRALIZED STAFFING COORDINATOR

BAPTIST HEALTH

Multitasking which included daily medical staffing for multiple locations. Responded to employee questions regarding schedules, timekeeping, and daily staffing.

2019-2023

EMERGENCY COMMUNICATIONS DISPATCHER

BRYANT COMMUNICATIONS

Multitasking which included documentation entry while radio, phone, and camera monitoring. Dispatched for fire, medical rescue, and police. Trained new dispatchers to ensure efficient communication and response times.

2018 – 2019

PHARMACY TECHNICIAN/FLOATER

CVS

Entered and filled patient prescriptions. Took calls and made calls to patients, doctors, and insurance companies. Engagement and enhancing customer experience. Responding to customers requests as needed. Orchestrated exemplary services by greeting customers courteously and offering assistance when needed

REFERENCES

LEE ANN CLEGHORN

CITY OF BRYANT

PHONE: 501-860-5191

SETH WAKEFIELD

CITY OF BRYANT

PHONE: 501-256-4129

TAYA COVEY

CITY OF BRYANT

PHONE: 501-860-8043